frontgate.com 2007-07-19

# Customer Service - For Your Protection - Frontgate

|  |   
  
|  |   
---|---  
|  |   
|  |  |  |  | 

|   
---  
| 

Online Security

Frontgate offers a secure online commerce environment. All credit transactions occur in a secure area of our site, protecting you from loss or misuse of information. The transfer of sensitive information between you and Frontgate is protected by the highest standard of encryption technology available on the Internet.

Public/private key cryptography enables the creation of a secure "conversation" between your browser and our secure server. While this conversation could potentially be "overheard," it cannot be decrypted.

**How You Can Tell You're Browsing a Secure Website**  
In order to be sure that information transferred between your browser and the Frontgate server is secure, it is important to be aware of the security information available to you through your browser.

Once you enter the Checkout process (when you're ready to purchase the items you have placed in your shopping cart), your connection to our server becomes secure. These security features are enacted automatically; you do not have to take any action to invoke them. To confirm that you are operating in secure mode, look at the bottom of your browser window. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser) you can be sure that your information is secure.

Example of a "closed lock" symbol in an Internet Explorer Browser:

Example of a "closed lock" symbol in a Netscape Communicator Browser:

You can also ensure security by checking the URL line of your browser. When you enter the secure area of our site, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https".

Example of a secure URL in an Internet Explorer Browser:

Example of a secure URL in a Netscape Communicator Browser:

**Data Encryption & Risk of Decryption**  
Frontgate makes use of a 128-bit encryption key issued by RSA Data Security, Inc. When a secure connection is initiated, our server's public key is automatically transferred to your browser. Your browser then uses this key to encrypt information transferred back to Frontgate. This information can only be decrypted using the private key installed on Frontgate's secure server.

You may have read in the news that the RC4 encryption algorithm had been broken. In fact, a single message which had been encrypted using the less powerful 40-bit key was successfully decrypted. However, decrypting this single message utilized 120 computer workstations and two parallel supercomputers spread across three major research centers for more than 8 days. Decrypting additional messages would take the same amount of time and resources. The 128-bit encryption key has not been broken.

**Top 10 Online Smart Shopping Tips**  
Visit the Direct Marketing Association's 

[_Top 10 Online Smart Shopping Tips_](http://www.shopthenet.org/tips.shtml) for safety tips and precautions to take when shopping online. The [_DMA Consumer Assistance Web site_](http://www.dmaconsumers.org/) also offers consumer protection information for shopping online, by phone, or by mail.

Contacting the Webmaster  
We've worked hard to bring you a secure online commerce environment, and we value your questions, comments, and concerns. If you have any feedback about our Web site security, please contact us 

 _via email_ or via regular mail:

FRONTGATE  
Webmaster  
5566 West Chester Road  
West Chester, OH 45069 

|   

---  
| 

Your Privacy

has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting our customers' personal information.

Those who communicate with and supply us with contact information may receive future communications by email, direct mail, or telephone. If you do not wish to receive correspondence from , you can contact us with a request to be removed from our mailing list.

This site recognizes the IP addresses of visitors, but not their email addresses. Individually identifiable email addresses are not captured or stored unless they are directly provided to us. Email addresses will NOT be provided to any non-affiliated parties outside of the business group.

**How We Gather & Use Your Personal Information**  
During your communications with , we use various methods of gathering your personal information to help ensure that your shopping experience is as efficient and accommodating as possible.

**Information We Gather**  
We collect information such as your name, billing and shipping addresses, phone number, email address, credit-card information, and certain demographic information. When you set up an online account with us, we also request a password to allow you secure access.

**How We Use Your Information**  
We utilize the information we receive in order to: 

  * Send catalogs you have requested and mailings that may be of interest to you, provided you have not requested otherwise 
  * Send exclusive email offers of new product announcements and special promotions, provided you have not opted out of receiving these notifications 
  * Process and track your orders 
  * Send order and shipping confirmation emails 
  * Tailor your experience at our site, presenting content customized to your interests 

You may terminate communications at any time by notifying us.

**How Our Web Site Uses Cookies & IP Addresses**  
Our site uses IP addresses to protect our customers' security and to gather broad geographic information. IP addresses do not disclose any other type of personal information, such as names or email addresses. 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. A cookie is a small data file stored on your computer. In order to shop at 's site, you must have cookies activated on your browser. Cookies identify your computer and allow us to personalize your shopping experience to best meet your interests. They do not contain any personal information. 

**Information Received by or Supplied to Third Parties**  
To better serve you and to enhance your shopping experience, we may supplement the information listed above with data that is publicly available and with data we receive from other reputable sources whose privacy policies meet the Direct Marketing Association's requirements.

From time to time, we may share our postal mailing list with carefully selected providers of goods and services that may be of interest to you. (If you prefer not to receive mailings from these providers, you can notify us at any time.) Also, on rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request in order to assist with fraud protection or investigation. Information is not provided to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

In order to protect our customers' security to the fullest extent, information for all orders is filtered by a third-party screening application.

**Changing Your Email & Mailing Preferences**  
If you are currently receiving communications from , it is because you have notified us of your desire to receive these mailings, because you have recently requested products or services from us, or because you have provided information to a third party affiliated with . If you prefer not to receive catalogs, email offers, or other communications from us, we give you the opportunity to terminate these mailings at any time. (Note: Because we plan our catalog and email mailings in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective.)

If you no longer wish to receive catalogs or mailings from affiliated companies, call 1.888.263.9850, contact us 

 _via email_, or send your mailing label to:

5566 West Chester Road  
West Chester, OH 45069 

If you no longer wish to receive email offers, visit our _Preferred Email Registry_ page to modify your preferences. You may also click on the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any of our emails. (Note: Your selection will apply only to the current corresponding email address. Please allow up to 90 days for the activation of any changes in address status. Future mailings may still be sent to alternate email addresses you may have supplied to us. Also, you may still receive confirmation and/or tracking emails if you place an order on our website.)

**Removing Your Name from Mailing Lists, Telemarketing Lists, & Email Lists in General**  
Most people enjoy receiving information about subjects that interest them or products and services they may need or want. Sometimes, however, the amount of this type of information - received by mail, phone or email - can become overwhelming. Visit the Direct Marketing Association's 

[_Consumer Assistance department_](http://www.dmaconsumers.org/) to find out how you can get your name removed from these types of lists.

**Making Corrections & Updates to Your Account Information**  
gives you the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:

  * Update your information in _My Account_.
  * Call one of our Customer Service Representatives at 1.888.263.9850.
  * Contact us  _via email_.

**Protecting Childrens' Privacy**  
The Web site is not intended for use by, nor do we knowingly collect personal information from, children under the age of 18.

**Contacting the Webmaster**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact us 

 _via email_, or write to us at:

Webmaster  
5566 West Chester Road  
West Chester, OH 45069 

|   

---  
| 

Our Quality Commitment & Price Guarantee

**Our Quality Commitment**  
At , our primary focus is quality. We guarantee that every product we sell will stand up to the supreme test — our customers' satisfaction.

Our One-Year Guarantee lets you put any product to the test. If for any reason you are not satisfied, simply return it within 90 days and we'll replace it or refund the cost of the item (excluding Shipping and Processing fees). In addition, we will repair or replace any product for a full year from the date of purchase.

**Price Guarantee**  
We have a high regard for value as well as quality. If you purchase from and see the same item in another catalog for less (including shipping and tax) within 90 days of your purchase, we'll gladly refund the difference. Please provide the other print catalog's advertisement and order form, and mail to:

Price Protection  
5566 West Chester Road  
West Chester, OH 45069 

**Instructions for Returns and Exchanges**

  1. Complete the Exchange/Return form that came with your order.
  2. Tear off the return shipping label from the bottom of the Exchange/Return form.
  3. Carefully repackage the merchandise and affix the return shipping label to the outside of your package.
  4. Return the package to us via UPS or insured parcel post.

If you do not have your Exchange/Return form, please send returns and exchanges to:

Customer Returns Department  
8879 Union Centre Blvd.  
West Chester, OH 45069 

Please note: Any items that are monogrammed, customized or made-to-order cannot be returned or exchanged unless damaged or defective.

**Questions?**  
Call 1.888.263.9850 or contact us 

 _via email_. |   

---  
| 

Cookies & JavaScript

Our site places a single, small file on your computer called a "cookie," which allows us to identify you as a unique visitor to our website. For example, if you have items in your shopping cart and leave our site or close your browser, the cookie helps us to identify you upon your return, so the contents of your cart will still be there for you. Your privacy and security are not compromised when you accept a cookie from our site. Cookies are encrypted and sent securely, and no personal information is collected by or stored within this cookie.

The Frontgate site also requires that JavaScript is enabled on your browser. Our servers use JavaScript to provide a more interactive shopping experience and to implement changes to the website. Enabling this coding language on your browser will not affect performance, nor will it collect or store any of your personal information.

To enable cookies and JavaScript, refer to the section that applies to your Internet platform and browser type: 

**Internet Explorer 6.0 and above (PC)**

To adjust scripting settings: 

  1. Select Internet Options from the Tools menu
  2. Click the Security tab
  3. Click the Internet Zone
  4. Click Custom Level
  5. Scroll to the Scripting section, and click Enable for each option
  6. Click OK to close the Security Settings window

To adjust cookie settings: 
  1. Click the Privacy tab
  2. In the Settings section, the vertical slider should be set to Medium
  3. Finishing up:
  4. Click Apply, then OK to close the Internet Options window
  5. Return to the previous page
  6. Click Refresh to re-load the Frontgate home page

**Internet Explorer 5.0 (PC)**

  1. Select Internet Options from the Tools menu
  2. Click the Security tab
  3. Click the Internet Zone
  4. Click Custom Level
  5. Scroll to the Cookies section, and click Enable for each option
  6. Scroll to the Scripting section, and click Enable for each option
  7. Click OK to close the Security Settings window
  8. Click OK to close the Internet Options window
  9. Return to the previous page
  10. Click Refresh to re-load the Frontgate home page

**Internet Explorer 4.x (PC)**

  1. Select Internet Options from the View menu
  2. Click the Advanced tab
  3. Scroll to the Security/Cookies section
  4. Click Always Accept Cookies
  5. Click OK to close the Internet Options window
  6. Return to the previous page
  7. Click Refresh to re-load the Frontgate home page

**Internet Explorer 5.0 and 4.x (Mac)**

  1. Select Preferences from the Edit menu
  2. Click Cookies from the scrolling menu
  3. Select Never Ask from the When Receiving Cookies menu
  4. Click Web Content from the Scrolling menu
  5. Select Enable Scripting from the Active Content box
  6. Click OK to close the Preferences window
  7. Return to the previous page
  8. Click Refresh to re-load the Frontgate home page

**Netscape 7.1 and above (PC or Mac)**

To adjust scripting settings: 

  1. Open the Edit menu and choose Preferences
  2. Under the Advanced category, click Scripts & Plugins (if no subcategories are visible, double-click Advanced to expand the list)
  3. Select the Scripts & Plugins preferences panel
  4. Under Enable JavaScript For, select the Navigator checkbox
  5. Under Allow scripts To, select the checkboxes for Create or Change Cookies and Read Cookies

To adjust cookie settings: 
  1. Open the Edit menu and choose Preferences
  2. Under the Privacy & Security category, click Cookies (if no subcategories are visible, double-click Privacy & Security to expand the list)
  3. Enable Cookies for Originating Web Site Only: select this option if you don't want to accept or return foreign cookies
  4. Enable Cookies Based on Privacy Settings: select this option if you handle cookies based on your privacy settings, then click the View button to confirm or modify your privacy settings
  5. Enable All Cookies: select this default option to permit all Web sites not explicitly blocked to set cookies on your computer
  6. Click OK to close the Preferences window
  7. Click Reload to re-load the Frontgate home page

**Netscape 4.0 (PC or Mac)**

  1. Select Preferences from the Edit menu
  2. Select Advanced from the Category menu
  3. Click Accept All Cookies
  4. Click Enable Javascript
  5. Click OK to close the Preferences window
  6. Return to the previous page
  7. Click Reload to re-load the Frontgate home page

**Customizing Privacy Settings in Internet Explorer 6.0**

In Internet Explorer 6.0, you can choose to allow cookies for individual sites while blocking others. This allows you to maximize your computers' privacy settings by not accepting cookies from any sites except the ones you specify. 

  1. In Internet Explorer, on the Tools menu, click Internet Options
  2. Click the Privacy tab, and then click Edit
  3. In Address of Web Site, type the complete address of the Web site for which you want to specify custom settings (i.e. http://www.microsoft.com)
  4. To specify that you want Internet Explorer to always allow cookies from the specified Web site to be saved on your computer, click Allow. To specify that you want Internet Explorer to never allow cookies from the specified Web site to be saved on your computer, click Block

**Notes:**

  * You can view a list of Web sites for which you have specified custom settings in the Managed Web Sites list. To remove a Web site from this list and delete its custom privacy settings, click Remove. When you remove a Web site from the Managed Web Sites list, your privacy settings for all Web sites without custom settings will be automatically applied to that Web site.
  * If you select a setting that does not allow cookies to be saved on your computer, you may not be able to view certain Web sites that require cookies.
  * When you change your privacy settings, the changes might not affect cookies that are already on your computer. To ensure that all of the cookies on your computer meet your privacy settings, you should delete all of the existing cookies on your computer. When you return to Web sites that previously had saved cookies on your computer, the Web sites that meet your privacy settings will again save cookies on your computer. The Web sites that do not meet your privacy settings will not be allowed to save cookies on your computer, and may not function properly.

|   
  
|  |   
|  | 

|  |
